<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>

	<atom:link href="http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/rss/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

	<title>ku.oc.yacedlaitnenopxe || exponentialdecay.co.uk</title>
	<link>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk</link>
	<description>Ross Spencer, C++ Developer</description>
	<category>C++ Developer</category>
	<language>en</language>
	<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>

	<item>
		<title>Beavis can you spare a dime?</title>
		<link>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk</link>
		<category>intro</category>
		<description>
			exponentialdecay.co.uk is currently undergoing a redesign to make
			it more mutable. RSS will form a part of that change so look for
			new stories to appear here in favor of less relevant news updates
			acting as deadweight over on the main website. come back soon. 
			--rs--
		</description>
		<dc:creator>--rs--</dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/guid1/</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Theory...</title>
		<link>http://kotaku.com/</link>
		<category>theory</category>
		<description>
			it might seem a little OTT writing so much in an RSS feed in favor
			of blogging up your main domain, but i guess i find that the beauty
			of RSS feeds. check out kotaku.com for their RSS feed. while they
			copy all their main content to RSS they do manage to convey most, if not
			all of a story through the feed cutting down on unecessary click-throughs
			and separating the wheat from the chaff for those just interested in the
			news. nice idea. --rs-- 
		</description>
		<dc:creator>--rs--</dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/guid2/</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Googlebot where are you..?</title>
		<link>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/images/johnny-5.jpg</link>
		<category>Bill Groundhog-Day, Ghostbustin'-ass Murray!</category>
		<description>
			Googlebot, c'mon man, it has been a frigging month, crawl my 
			site dude! - seriously, there might not be a lot going on here
			but at least take note of some of the new HTML elements I'm using
			and the RSS feed, RSS man! Peace. --rs-- 
		</description>
		<dc:creator>--rs--</dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 22:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/guid3/</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>beta...</title>
		<link>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/beta/</link>
		<category>beta</category>
		<category>xml/xslt</category>
		<description>
			exponentialdecay.co.uk || beta is up and running. The site is an
			exact duplicate of the main website, this is to exhibit the use
			of XML and XSL technologies to output a valid XHTML document. In time
			the same technologies are going to be used to output this site in
			numerous other formats including text only.
			&lt;/p&gt;
			Have a look at the page. Overall it has ported fairly well. In future
			the XML can be modified to be much more generic, thus allowing the 
			transformation to be much simpler. I reckon I can get the amount of code
			used down to about 1/4 of its current usage. Designing for XML/XSLT in
			the first place will be a big step toward achieving that.
			--rs--
		</description>
		<dc:creator>--rs--</dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid>http://www.exponentialdecay.co.uk/guid4/</guid>
	</item>	
	
</channel>
</rss> 
